Friedlander, Walter A.; Papers ger003
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Correspondence files, 1918-1984; 2; 3,383 folders
  - Professional correspondence, 1933-1984; 2.2; 1391 folders containing approx. 21,788 items of correspondence
    - Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, including some with former students), 1933-1984; 2.2.2; 1043 folders containing approx. 6835 items of correspondence
      - Conlee, LaVonne, 1971 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 221)
      - Cooper, Elaine Abrams, 1964 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 222)
      - Cooper, Ruth, undated (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 223)
      - Cooper, Shirley, 1979 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 224)
      - Cordemann, Margarete, 1958 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 225)
      - Correa de Camacho, Silvia, 1970 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 226)
      - Cortese, Carla, 1957 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 227)
      - Costarella, Sylvia, 1956-1972 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 228)
        Costarella, John.
      - Costin, Lela B., 1973-1983 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 229)
      - Couder, Bruno, 1979 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 230)
      - * Cowgill, Donald O.
      - Cramer, Hanna, 1978 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 231)
        Crane, John A. see Society for the Study of Social Problems
      - Cudaback, Dorothea (Dot), 1970-1982 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 232)
      - Cukerbaum, Bernard, 1941 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 233)
      - Cumming, Roger, 1963 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 234)
      - Czechoslovakia, 1980 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 235)
      - Dare, Claudia, 1982 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 236)
      - Darling, Gale, 1955 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 237)
      - Das Gupta, Jyotrinda, 1977 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 238)
      - Dasbach, Fernando (Fred), 1970-1972 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 239)
      - Daube, David, 1974-1975 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 240)
      - Davidson, George F., 1954 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 241)
      - Davies, Robert, 1982 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 242)
      - Davis, Calvin, 1965 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 243)
      - Davis, Elizabeth, 1947-1949 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 244)
      - Davis, Michael, 1969 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 245)
      - de Baan, Eberhard, 1976 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 246)
      - Decken, Margret von der, 1954-1960 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 247)
      - de Cnyf, Maurice, 1958-1961 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 248)
      - Degener, Gustav, 1946-1947 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 249)
      - de Hurtado, Isabel, 1956 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 250)
      - Deimling, Gerhard, 1977-1982 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 251)
      - de Jongh, Dasja, 1972-1983 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 252)
      - de Lange, Harry M., 1972-1980 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 253)
      - DeLee, Flora, 1927-1945 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 254)
      - Demême, Yvonne, 1936 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 255)
      - Demme, Dagmar, 1979 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 256)
      - deMorsier, J.M. (Save the Children International Union; Union Internationale de Secours aux Enfants), 1938-1942 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 257)
      - * Dentler, Robert
      - de Riel, Juergen, 1949 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 258)
      - Derkach, Nadia, 1975 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 259)
      - Despite Everything, 1965 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 260)
      - * Deutscher, Irwin
      - Devereaux, Charles, 1948-1963 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 261)
      - DeVoe, Dorsh Marie, 1983 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 262)
      - DeWitt, Florence, 1954-1960 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 263)
      - Diamond, Bernard L., 1965 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 264)
      - Diamond, Jed, 1966 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 265)
      - Dieck, Margret, 1979-1981 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 266)
      - Dieckmann, Karl Josef, 1974 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 267)
      - Dobrogoiski, Martha von, 1957-1962 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 268)
      - Dodds, Dicy, 1956 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 269)
      - Doerr, William, 1960-1962 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 270)
      - Dolls, Margot, 1976-1978 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 271)
      - Dorman, Granville P., 1953 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 272)
      - Dorst, Brigitte, 1982-1984 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 273)
      - * Dove, James R.
      - Drath, Martin, 1957-1958 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 274)
      - Drechsler, Michael, 1957-1982 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 275)
        Drechsler, Waldtraut.
        Drechsler, Suse, 1948.
      - Drucker, Adolph B., 1951-1964 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 276)
      - Drucker, Lisbeth, 1934-1935 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 277)
      - Drucker, Peter F., 1955 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 278)
      - Dumpson, James R., 1961-1969 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 279)
      - Duning, Arthur, 1957-1982 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 280)
      - Durand-Wever, Anne-Marie, 1955-1960 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 281)
      - Dvorsky, Camille, 1971 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 282)
      - * Eades, Joe
      - Eaton, Joseph W., 1961-1964 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 283)
      - Eberhard, Alide, 1960-1982 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 284)
        Eberhard, Wolfram.
      - Eberhard, Kurt, 1973-1974 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 285)
      - Eckstein, Charlotte, 1963 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 286)
      - Eden, Ilse, 1974-1982 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 287)
      - Edinger, Dora, 1960-1963 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 288)
      - Edinger, Lewis J., 1961 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 289)
      - Egli, Robert (Zeitschrift für Präventivmedizin), 1955-1958 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 290)
      - Ehlers, Adolf, 1965-1974 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 291)
      - Ehrenfried, Lilli, 1933-1955 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 292)
      - Ehrenzweig, Albert A., 1961-1966 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 293)
        Ehrenzweig, Erika, 1948, 1974.
      - Ehrlich, Ernst Ludwig, 1945 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 294)
      - Ehrlich-Landé, Lilli, 1933 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 295)
      - Ehrmann, Henry W., 1940-1942 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 296)
      - Eichelbaum, Herta, 1960; 1982 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 297)
      - Eilers, Elfriede, 1973-1981 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 298)
      - * Eisgruber, Elsa
        See Schott-Fiechtl, Elsa
      - Eklund, Helen, 1979 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 299)
      - Elder, Joseph W., 1976 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 300)
      - Elkan, Otto, 1920 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 301)
      - Ellmar, Paul, 1933 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 302)
      - Engel, Frank, 1978 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 303)
      - Enochs, Elizabeth Shirley, 1946-1964 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 304)
      - Eran, Yechiel, 1981 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 305)
      - Erko, Walter, 1962-1984 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 306)
      - Erlich, Sasia, 1933-1934 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 307)
      - Erlich, Vera S., 1961 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 308)
      - Eska, Brunhilde, 1980 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 309)
      - Evans, Austin P., 1943 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 310)
      - Exarchos, Kay, 1970-1984 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 311)
      - Eyferth, Hanns, 1951-1977 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 312)
      - Falck, Hans S., 1965-1979 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 313)
      - Falk, Alfred, 1945-1949 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 314)
      - Farr, Shirley, 1939-1940 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 315)
      - Fasolo, Emma, 1965-1983 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 316)
      - Faure, Paul, 1933 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 317)
      - * Fechenbach, Irma
        See Fey, Irma
      - Feibel, Charlotte (Lotte), 1935-1965 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 318)
      - Feidel-Mertz, Hildegard, 1977-1982 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 319)
      - Feige, Rudolf, 1949-1983 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 320)
      - Feiger, Ilse, 1960-1969 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 321)
        Feiger, Philip.
      - Feldman, Gerald D., 1972-1978 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 322)
      - Feldman, Ronald, 1966-1973 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 323)
        Feldman, Dina.
      - Fenge, Horst, 1976 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 324)
      - * Fenichel, Otto
        See Laub, Rose.
      - Fenselau, Otto, 1947 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 325)
      - Ferguson, Bertha, 1972; 1980 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 326)
      - Feuer, Lewis S., 1966-1976 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 327)
      - Fey (Fechenbach), Irma, 1933-1950 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 328)
      - Fibush, Esther, 1965 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 329)
      - Fichtner, Otto (Deutscher Verein für öffentliche und private Fürsorge), 1970-1983 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 330)
      - Fiebig, Udo, 1979 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 331)
      - Fijalkowski, Jürgen, 1963-1965 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 332)
      - Finkle, Evelyn, 1952-1983 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 333)
        Finkle, Bernard (Bud).
      - Finney, Eleanor, 1954-1981 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 334)
        Finney, Frank.
      - Firestone, Mose, 1951-1983 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 335)
        Firestone, Ruth.
      - Fischel, Wesley R., 1959 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 336)
      - Fischer, Alice, 1967-1969 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 337)
      - Fixel, Justine, 1962-1966 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 338)
      - Flath, Klaus, 1966-1967 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 339)
      - Fletcher, Nancy, 1963-1964 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 340)
        Fletcher, A.G.
      - Florsheim, Dorothea (Dora), 1933-1948 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 341)
      - Förster, Hilde, 1965-1983 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 342)
      - Fogel, David, 1970-1973 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 343)
      - * Foote, Nelson N.
      - Formichi, Virginia, 1972-1984 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 344)
      - Forster, Edgar, 1981 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 345)
      - Forthman, Robert, 1978-1982 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 346)
      - Foster, Frank, 1938-1946 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 347)
      - * Fox, Byron
      - Fränkel, Hermann, 1938-1939 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 348)
      - Francel, Edward, 1963-1972 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 349)
      - Frankenstein, Ernst, 1934 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 350)
      - Franks, Else D., 1944-1947 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 351)
        Franks, Gerald E.Fstrauss
      - Franz, Wolfgang, 1983 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 352)
      - Frazier, Thomas L., 1961 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 353)
      - * French, David G.
      - Freund, Hugo, 1937-1957 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 354)
      - Freundlich, Otto, 1935-1947 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 355)
        Freundlich, Hannah.
      - Freyh, Brigitte, 1970 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 356)
      - Frick, Renate, 1957-1959 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 357)
        Frick, Hans.
      - Friedeberg, Ursula, 1937-1939 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 358)
      - Friedländer, Hans, 1953-1954 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 359)
      - Friedman, David B. (Kaiser Foundation Hospital), 1954-1971 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 360)
        Friedman, Alma.
      - * Friedsam, J.H.
      - Friesenhahn, Ernst, 1957-1959 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 361)
      - Fritz, Anna S., 1982 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 362)
      - Frölich, Rosi, 1973-1979 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 363)
      - Fukuyama, Kazuma Yoda, 1976-1983 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 364)
      - * Funke, Else
        See Deutscher Berufsverband der Sozialarbeiter und Sozialpädagogen e.V.
      - Furck, Carl-Ludwig, 1966-1973 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 365)
      - Gaede, Maria, 1952 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 366)
      - Gallagher, Patricia, 1963-1981 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 367)
      - Galper, Jeffrey, 1976 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 368)
      - Gamboni, Elizabeth (Betty), 1971-1984 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 369)
      - Gambrill, Eileen, 1978-1981 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 370)
      - Gamp, Christa, 1952-1967 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 371)
      - * Gans, Herbert
      - Gaupp, Peter G., 1966 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 372)
      - Gebhard, Bruno, 1978-1984 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 373)
      - Gehrmann, Friedhelm, 1980-1981 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 374)
      - * Geis, Gilbert L.
      - * Geisman, Ludwig L.
      - Gelfken, Tami, 1930-1935 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 375)
      - George, K. N., 1961-1981 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 376)
      - George, Manfred, 1943-1965 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 377)
        See also Aufbau (NY).
      - Gerechter, Gerhard, 1953 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 378)
      - Gerstung, Rudolf, 1934-1958 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 379)
        Gerstung, Grethe, 1957-1965.
      - Gibson, Dorothy, 1965-1979 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 380)
      - Giovannoni, Jeanne, 1973-1983 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 381)
      - Glaser, Kurt, 1934-1977 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 382)
        Glaser, Emily.
      - Gleisner, Martin (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 383)
      - Glikman, Esther, 1957-1978 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 384)
        Glikman, Horace.
        Glikman, Georges, 1979.
      - Goebel, Ernst-Karl, 1927-1933 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 385)
      - Goelke, Elfriede, 1933 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 386)
      - Goldenberg, Natalie, 1940-1959 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 387)
        Goldenberg, Leon.
      - Goldhart, Gerda, 1957 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 388)
      - Goldmann, Franz, 1951-1957 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 389)
      - Goldstein, Julius, 1939-1970 (Box 16 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 390)
        Goldstein, Hanna, 1939-1984.
      - * Goldstein, Lewis
      - Goodman, Mark Joseph, 1975 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 391)
      - Gordon, Bonnie, 1962 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 392)
      - Gordon, Margaret S., 1964; 1967 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 393)
      - Gorges, Renate, 1981 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 394)
      - Gotthelf, Herta, 1948-1949 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 395)
      - Grab, Walter, 1976-1982 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 396)
      - Gramm, Hermann, 1964-1965 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 397)
      - Grandjean, E., 1959 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 398)
      - Grebing, Helga, 1973 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 399)
      - Greene, Rachel, 1946 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 400)
      - * Grelfer, Julian L.
      - Griffith, George L., 1966 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 401)
      - Grillo, Evelio, 1959-1979 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 402)
      - Grobleben, Harald, 1981 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 403)
      - Gröttrup, Bernd, 1979 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 404)
      - Gronemann, Frieda, 1933 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 405)
      - Gruenbaum, Luther, 1958-1959 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 406)
      - Guenther, Louise, 1949 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 407)
      - Gumbel, Emil J., 1935-1962 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 408)
        Gumbel, Marieluise.
      - Gundelman, Sylvia, 1978-1983 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 409)
      - Gupta, Banwari Lal, 1970-1972 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 410)
      - Gur-Bax, Gope, 1955 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 411)
      - Gurin, Arnold, 1962 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 412)
      - Gurland, Arcadius R. L., 1961 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 413)
      - Gutkind, Peter C. W., 1964 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 414)
      - Haas, Ernst B., 1971-1978 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 415)
      - Haase-Schur, Ilse, 1976-1977 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 416)
      - Haaser, Paula, 1952 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 417)
      - Hachenburg, Hans, 1951 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 418)
      - Hachenburg, Max, 1947-1948 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 419)
      - Hadula, Werner, 1958-1962 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 420)
        Hadula, Wera.
      - Häfelin, Ursula, 1960-1963 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 421)
        Häfelin, Ulrich.
      - Hänchen, Ursula, 1971-1981 (Box 17 (2.2.2-Professional correspondence (lesser amounts, ), Folder 422)